vanderlande.com 2015-03-15

# Privacy Policy - Vanderlande

This is the Privacy Policy of Vanderlande Industries B.V (hereinafter: ‘Vanderlande Industries’). This statement explains how Vanderlande Industries deals with personal data that is obtained via the websites www.vanderlande.nl, www.vanderlande.de and www.vanderlande.com (hereinafter: ‘the Websites’) and personal data that is obtained via an offline request for information or contact. 

### YOUR PERSONAL DATA IS SECURE AT VANDERLANDE INDUSTRIES 

Vanderlande Industries respects the privacy of its customers, business relations and users of its Websites and services and ensures that any personal information it receives will be protected and treated confidentially. The processing of certain categories of personal data is reported to the Dutch Data Protection Authority [College Bescherming Persoonsgegevens] under 1528652 in accordance with the Dutch Personal Data Protection Act [Wet bescherming persoonsgegevens]. 

### COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONAL DATA

REQUEST FOR CONTACT OR INFORMATION  
If you are curious about what Vanderlande Industries could do for you, please contact Vanderlande Industries (head office) or a local branch in another country. This can be done both by telephone and via the online contact form on the Websites.

ONLINE CONTACT FORM  
If you request Vanderlande Industries to provide information, make contact or schedule an appointment with you, you will need to provide at least the following personal data via the online contact form in order for this request to be processed: 

  * Area of interest
  * Company
  * Name
  * E-mail address

Depending on your request or question, you may also be asked to provide the following personal data: 

  * Position
  * Telephone number (if you wish Vanderlande Industries to call you)
  * Country

DOWNLOAD FORM  
Additional information about the products and solutions of Vanderlande Industries in various areas can be downloaded via the Websites. In order to download this information, you will need to provide at least the following personal data via the online download form: 

  * First name and surname
  * E-mail address
  * Company

This data is collected so that we can gain insight into interest in certain products and solutions of Vanderlande Industries and contact you, if necessary.

REGISTRATION FOR EVENTS  
It is possible to register for events that are being organised and/or attended by Vanderlande Industries via the Websites. You can register via an online registration form, for which you will need to provide at least the following personal data: 

  * Name 
  * Company name
  * Address details (for sending tickets)
  * Position
  * Country
  * E-mail address
  * Telephone number (if you wish Vanderlande Industries to call you)

You can request Vanderlande Industries to contact you via the online registration form in order to make an appointment at the Vanderlande stand during the relevant event. You can also ask questions or make comments.

The data will be processed for the purpose of the relevant event, e.g. for sending tickets, and to contact you, if necessary.

E-MAIL NEWSLETTER   
If you wish to receive Vanderlande Industries’ free e-mail newsletter, you will need to provide at least the following personal data:

  * First name and surname
  * E-mail address
  * Area of interest

This data will be used to send you the free e-mail newsletter and to contact you, if necessary. 

### COOKIES

The Websites make use of cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is sent together with a website page and stored via your browser on the hard drive of your computer, tablet or telephone.   
Please refer to our cookie policy for more information about the use of cookies on the Websites. The cookie policy explains how the Websites make use of cookies, where the cookies come from and why they are used.  

### PROVISION TO BRANCHES OF VANDERLANDE INDUSTRIES

In order to provide you with a better service, your personal data may be made available to local branches of Vanderlande Industries, including branches in countries outside the European Economic Area (‘EEA’). These branches will use your data solely for the purposes for which it has been provided, e.g. for the performance of an agreement that has been concluded with you or for providing information that you have requested. 

### VANDERLANDE INDUSTRIES DOES NOT PROVIDE YOUR DATA TO THIRD PARTIES

Vanderlande Industries will not provide your personal data to third parties, unless: 

  * you have given express consent for this purpose;
  * it is necessary for the performance of an agreement concluded with Vanderlande Industries;
  * it is compulsory or permitted by law; or
  * it is necessary for preventing or combating fraud.

### RETENTION PERIOD

Vanderlande Industries will not retain your data longer than is necessary for the purposes for which it is processed, unless the data must be retained longer in order to comply with statutory obligations (such as a retention obligation). The length of time for which data is retained depends on the nature of the data and the purposes for which it is processed. The retention period can thus differ for each purpose. 

### SECURITY

When it is processing personal data, Vanderlande Industries always maintains a security level that is adequate, in view of the latest technical developments, to prevent unauthorised access to, adaptation, disclosure or loss of personal data.

The security of your personal data is obviously also based on keeping the login details of your account (username and password) confidential. Never share your login details with anyone else and always take care when using them. 

### PERUSAL AND CORRECTION OF YOUR DATA

You are entitled to peruse the personal information that Vanderlande Industries holds in relation to you. If the information is incorrect, you may request Vanderlande Industries to correct it. Such requests for perusal or correction of your data can be addressed in the following ways to Vanderlande Industries, accompanied by a copy of a valid form of identification: 

  * by e-mail: marcom(at)vanderlande.com or
  * in writing: Vanderlande Industries, FAO Marketing and Communications, Vanderlandelaan 2, 5466 RB Veghel.

You can also use these addresses for any questions.

If you have an online account at Vanderlande Industries, you can always view and, if necessary, adjust your data and personal settings by logging in and adjusting your account settings. 

### RIGHT TO OBJECT

You can object free of charge to the use of your personal data. Your objection to the use of your personal data can be sent by e-mail or in writing to Vanderlande Industries at the above addresses. You will receive a written response from Vanderlande Industries within four weeks.

If you object to the use of your data for direct marketing purposes, Vanderlande Industries shall immediately cease to use your data for these purposes.

### PRIVACY POLICY OF THIRD PARTIES

This Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party websites that are associated with the Websites by means of links. Vanderlande Industries does not accept any responsibility or liability with regard to how these third parties deal with your personal data. Vanderlande Industries therefore recommends that you always familiarise yourself with the privacy policy on the websites concerned. 

### AMENDMENTS

This Privacy Policy may be amended. The most up-to-date version of the Privacy Policy can always be found on the Websites. Vanderlande Industries therefore recommends that you regularly consult this Privacy Policy, in any event before you provide personal data to Vanderlande Industries. 

### QUESTIONS

Vanderlande Industries is happy to assist you further if you have any questions or comments relating to the above.  
Vanderlande Industries B.V.  
Vanderlandelaan 2  
5466 RB Veghel (NL)

Telephone: +31 (0)413 49 49 49  
Fax: +31 (0)413 36 29 10  
E-mail: info@vanderlande.com 

© 2012 Vanderlande Industries B.V., all rights reserved.
